Guide to the Nelson J. Shaulis papers, 1941-1986.
Shaulis, Nelson J. papers, 1941-1986
- Slides - Box 2, gibberellic acid, depression of growth, 1959-1960 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 2, Gibrel, seeded, 1957-1959 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 2, Gibrel, currants, 1957-1958 (Box 27)
- (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 2, NAR-59, 1958-1959 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 2, NAR-60, 1958-1964 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 2, NAR-1961, 1958-1961 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 2, Vinifera, 1958-1961 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 2, C. Pratt, berry size, 1958-1959 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 2, spacing (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 2, berry growth (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 2, fruit setting experiments (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, potassium deficiency, 1948-1960 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, potassium scorch, 1941-1959 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, 805 color (Box 27)
  Slides wrapped in paper measurement diagrams
- Slides - Box 3, potassium, black leaf, 1941-1969 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, potassium and magnesium deficiency combination, 1951-1953 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, manganese deficiency, 1949-1960 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, soils, Taylor-Boynton Harding experiment, 1949-1956 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, leaf analysis (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, nitrogen, 1952-1959 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, pomace (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, iron deficiency, 1950-1974 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, phosphorous, 1950-1956 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, zinc deficiency (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, magnesium deficiency, 1948-1971 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, boron toxicity and deficiency, 1951-1956 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, fertilizers (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, boron deficiency, 1956 (Box 27)
- Slides - Box 3, water, 1947-1949 (Box 27)
- Slides - Washington and California grapes, ca.1950 (Box 27)
- Slides - Pruning, training, trellising (Box 27)
- Slides - Mulch (Box 27)
- Slides - Grapes lysimeters (Box 27)
- Glass slide plates (Box 27)
  Fragile - glass
- Slides - Currants, ca. 1953-1957 (Box 27)
- Slides - Currants, ca. 1953-1956 (Box 27)
- Slides - California trip, August, 1957 (Box 27)
- Slides - Pennsylvania peach work (Box 27)
- Slides - California and Washington Box, California, 1954-1960 (Box 27)
- Slides - California and Washington Box, Caifornia, thompson seedless, 1967 (Box 27)
- Slides - California and Washington Box, California, mechanized pruning, 1960-1963 (Box 27)
- Slides - California and Washington Box, California, weeds and weed control, 1963-1965 (Box 27)
- Slides - California and Washington Box, California, frost protection, 1961-1964 (Box 27)
- Slides - California and Washington Box, California, general scenes, 1965-1969 (Box 27)
- Slides - California and Washington Box, California, nematode injury, 1954-1960 (Box 27)
- Slides - California and Washington Box, California, virus, ca. 1954-1956 (Box 27)
- Slides - California and Washington Box, Kissler training work, etc., 1966-1969 (Box 27)
- Slides - California and Washington Box, Washington grapes, 1950 (Box 27)
- Slides - California and Washington Box, travel from California to New York, August 1969 (Box 27)
- Slides - California and Washington Box, Prosser Washington grapes, 1950, August 1969 (Box 27)
  Includes 1950 slides from Kennewick, Washington and various vineyards
- Slides - California and Washington Box, Perth, Washington etc., 1965-1968 (Box 27)
- Slides - California and Washington Box, station collection, 1964-1967 (Box 27)
- Pom cards, 1950s-1970s (Box 28)
  Most cards from 1970s. Includes pom cards for viticulture book
- Pom cards - Experimental vineyard rejuvenator, 1956 (Box 28)
- Pom cards - Muscadine, 1973 (Box 28)
- Pom cards - Experimental weed control, 1952 (Box 28)
- Pom cards - Light intensity and fruitfulness in Concord, 1970 (Box 28)
- Pom cards - Experimental row width (Box 28)
- Pom cards - Experimental Biotron, ca. 1965 (Box 28)
- Pom cards - Experimental Alar (Box 28)
- Pom cards - Vine management (pruning, training, spacing), 1952-1972 (Box 28)
  File tab included date of October 1979
- Pom cards - Rootstocks and vine growth, 1954-1968 (Box 28)
- Pom cards - Growth regulation efforts, berry size and fruit set, 1958-1970 (Box 28)
- Pom cards - Morphology and anatomy, book candidate, 1963 (Box 28)
- Pom cards - roots, growth and growth chambers, ca. 1963-1966 (Box 28)
- Pom cards - Abnormalities, 1974-1979 (Box 28)
- Pom cards - Cold injury, 1952-1973 (Box 28)
  File tab included date of November 1979
- Pom cards - GDC, 1963-1966 (Box 28)
- Pom cards - Light and temperature in vineyard (Box 28)
- Grape costs, 1960-1980 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Grape costs, for Penn Yan speech, 1971-1974 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Grape costs, the Cost of Production paper, etc., 1948, 1974-1977 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Freezes, graph cold damage, 1932-1962, 1976-1981 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Science in agriculture, volume XX, number 1, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  Note reads "Use book regarding erosion"
- Grape varieties for cool climates, ca. 1991-1993 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1971-1997 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Canopies, 1980-1984 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Italy, Turin text, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Italy, C. Intrieri, 1981-1988 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Italy, Torno, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- New York grape statistics, 1980-1996 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- New York winery surveys, 1955, 1973-1993 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Agricultural photographs and topographical sheets, ca. 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Geography and maps, book, ca. 1979-1974 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Alar, 1931-1976 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Gibberellin, 1967-1975 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Phenology, New York concords, ca. 1972-1981 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Leaf water potential, 1966-1977 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Root produced cytokinins, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Cold injury, 1975-1976, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Berry size, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Oregon speech and trip, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Examination of grape crop control techniques other than solely by pruning in the dormant season, memo, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Controllong phylloxera, 1953-1977 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Pom 7126, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Photosynthesis rates, Germany and Switzerland, 1963-1975 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Rootstocks (ENA), ca. 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Pollutants, ca. 1966-1976 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Literature to give to LEGS advisory committee, 1970-1980 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Canopy management, 1983-1985 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Vine photosynthesis, 1955-1968 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Vine photosynthesis, 1970-1981 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Vine photosynthesis, translocation (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Newspaper clippings, articles, and bulletins, 1953-1976 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Slides - Young vines, 1962-1973 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Slides - Yield analysis, 1951-1977 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Slides - Weeds, 1944-1977 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  Includes letter from Monsanto regarding weed slides provided to Nelson Shaulis
- Slides - Viticulture, general, 1948-1977 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Slides - Vine size, 1969-1973 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Slides - Variety, 1962-1976 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Slides - Training, 1949-1976 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Slides - Structure, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  Also includes two cal. dating diagrams
- Slides - Spacing, training, and shoot direction, 1965-1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Slides - Site and soil erosion, 1951-1983 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Slides - Pruning, 1961-1977 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Slides - Shoot positioning, 1969-1973 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Slides - Shoot growth, cane quality, 1968-1974 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Slides - Rougeon abnormality, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Slides - Roots, 1963-1967 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Slides - Rootstocks and replant, 1951-1969 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Slides - Propagation, 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Slides - Muscadines, 1950, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Slides - Mechanization, harvest and pruning, 1960-1975 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Slides - Maturity, 1959-1973 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Slides - Machinery, ca. 1966 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Slides - Leaves and leaf area, 1958-1977 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Slides - Injuries, 1947-1978 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Slides - Growth regulators, 1958-1977 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Slides - Glyphosate, 1959-1976 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Slides - POM 304 Fruiting Physiology, 1958-1970 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Slides - Equipment, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Slides - Deficiencies ( potassium, magnesium, boron, iron, manganese, zinc), 1949-1987 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Slides - Crop thinning and stress, 1966-1973 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Slides - Cold injury, 1933-1981 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Slides - Cluster chart and trait set, abnormal and berries for seeds, Concord, 1948-1981 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Slides - Climate, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Slides - Chemical comp., ca. 1961-1967 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Slides - Canopy climate and architechture, 1953-1976 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Slides - Biotron, 1959-1970 (Box 30, Folder 35)
- Slides - Australia, Israel, California, Hawaii, Germany, 1961, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  Mostly 1967 Sultana slides
- Slides - Boron deficiency and iron deficiency, photo, book, 1980-1984 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  Note mentioning book "Viticulture Book 1973-" included on a tab in this folder. Includes notes on October 1981 photography.
- Slides - Unfiled, 1963-1988 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  Includes 1980 APS slide set #29 and syllabus for Grape Diseases
- Slides - Mechanization, Seyval, 1970-1991 (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Slides - Vine growth, canopies, yield equations, acid studies, soils, ca. 1979-1986 (Box 30, Folder 40)
- Speech, South Africa, ca. 1988 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  Includes slides
- Cornell seminars on phosphorous, 1940-1941 (Box 31)
  Bound collection of lectures by various professors
- Viticulture for Northeastern North America, book draft, ca. 1977-1980 (Box 31)
- Leaf area amount, 1968-1977 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Canopy, book, ca. 1954-1980 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  Includes 2 photographs of canopies, Merbein, Victoria
- Spacing, 1922-1977 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Leaf analysis and visual symptoms, ca. 1959-1970 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Metric conversions regarding viticulture (Box 31, Folder 5)
- OIV-Capetown paper, 1982-1988 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Vine variability, Peter May and Nelson Shaulis, 1970-1972 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Arkansas, 1974-1976 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- ASE program and notes, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Brainstorming, viticulture, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Open house, Fredonia, NY, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Scald on Catawbas, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Concord planting stock Mead and maps, 1960-1961 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Tour and speak out, May 17, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Niagara grape project memorandum of understanding, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Peter May visit, 1971, 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- S.5898 fruiting problem, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Glyphosate - Soil, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Propagation, ca. 1969 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Oxidant Stipple, 1969-1972 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Muscadines, 1948, 1973-1980 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Vine development, book, 1949-1959 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Italy - Program and viticulture, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  Includes photos of Seminar on Mechanical Pruning held in Motta di Livenza
- Grape virus diseases, 1958-1975 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Geneva weather records, April 1970 - October 1970 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Geneva weather records, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Geneva weather records, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- Geneva weather records, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Geneva weather records, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Geneva weather records, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Geneva weather records, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- Geneva weather records, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- Geneva weather records, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 33)
- Geneva weather records, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 34)
- New York State grape production research fund, 1955-1976 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- Terminology - Canopy, 1985-1988 (Box 31, Folder 36)
- Pruning severity, 1948-1990 (Box 31, Folder 37)
- South African Journal for Enology and Viticulture, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 38)
- American Viticulture and Enology Research Network (AVERN), 1996 (Box 31, Folder 39)
- Spacing abstract, ca. 1996 (Box 31, Folder 40)
- Wind, 1955-1958, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 41)
- Hardiness of cane, primary and secondary buds, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 42)
- Rootstocks, grafting, 1947-1979 (Box 31, Folder 43)
- Nutritional composition and fertilizers, 1956-1991 (Box 31, Folder 44)
- American Wine Society, 1982-1988 (Box 31, Folder 45)
- Descriptive Measures of New York Wine Grape Growing, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  Includes photo and map of North Bass island 1950-1951
- Pest management, 1957-1979 (Box 31, Folder 47)
- Growth regulators, includes Alar and Giberellin, 1957-1989 (Box 31, Folder 48)
- Cost of production, 1936-1958 (Box 31, Folder 49)
- French American Hybrid names, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 50)
- Lincoln College, New Zealand seminar, January 1988 (Box 31, Folder 51)
  Includes poster from Lincoln College viticulture and wine science program
- Expanded Statewide Viticulture Program, April 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Propagation of grapes, Pomology department, 1945-1969 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Brewer's work on air pollution, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Statistics, Chautauqua-Erie, 1966-1976 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Giberellin treatment on Delaware, partial translation from Japanese, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Canopy length, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Lake Erie Generating Station, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Leaf and soil analysis, 1969, 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- David G. Himerick, Fruit Grower, October 1985 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Class planning, POM 307 and POM 307, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Photography sheet notes, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Row 291 Crop record, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Shoot direction, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- A Viticultural Examination of 1984-1988 Production of Ripe Grapes in Upstate New York, Taylor Wine Company, growers meeting, May 19, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Grape production research, 1966, 1980-1984 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- General documents, 1938, ca.1967-1985 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Soil Management (Box 32, Folder 17)
  Includes transparencies
- Vigueur, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Optimum Characteristics of Canopy and Related Practices, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  Includes research and outline only
- Mechanical Pruning of Grapevines, manuscript draft, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- 1978 Grape Research, Horticultural Research Institute of Ontario, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Literature references, 1963-1969 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Variety development sheet, ca. 1963 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous documents regarding book, May 1984 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Experimental trellis wire project, 1962-1968 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Untersuchungen zur Behebung von Zink-Mangel bei Rieslingreben an der Mosel duch Blattdüngung mir Wuchsal, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Changes in Photosynthesis and Respiration during Berry Development in Relation to the Ripening of Delaware Grapes, by Yoshiyuki Numi and Hirotaka Torikata, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- N.Y. Viticulture Seen as a Complex of Research-Oriented Decisions, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Grapevine census data, 1900-1954 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Yield factors, 1972-1975 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Chardonnay data, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous data, ca. 1939-1982 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- Vineyard 3, book 2, rows 16-33, New York State Agricultural Experimental Station, Division of Meteorology, Cornell University weather observations, Lake Keuka Region, NY, 1960-1962 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- York, PA speech, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- Michigan Partridge speech material, 1929-1988 (Box 32, Folder 35)
- Partridge outline and speech, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- Partridge speech - literature bulletins, 1911-1958,1989 (Box 32, Folder 37)
- Partridge manuscript, replaced, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 38)
- Michigan mechanization speech, 1988-1992 (Box 32, Folder 39)
- Michigan mechanization manuscript, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 40)
- York PA Speech (Box 32, Folder 41)
- Paper from Hungary mechanization conference - Management of grapevines, including Geneva double curtain trained grapevines for a more mechanized viticulture, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 42)
- Pom cards, 1970s (Box 33)
  Includes R. Smart thesis figures photos
- Pom cards, 1950s-1960s (Box 33)
  Includes equipment photos
- Index cards (Box 33)
  Includes citations, glossary definitions (some alphabetized), afew cards with data and diagrams, a couple business cards, notes
- Slides - Aurore, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Slides and notes - Glyphosate, October 1975 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Slides - Weather shelter, for book, October 1978 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Slides - GDC in Vineyard 23, Geneva, May 17, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Slides - S.5898 lesson, mid-June, June 1974 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Slides - Potassium deficiency, book, October 1978 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Slides - S.5898, July 1974 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Slides - book, potassium deficiency, glyphosate injury, October 1975 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- "Book" photos guide (Box 34, Folder 9)
  Appears to indicate individual POM card numbers
- John Handerberg, Portland, NY (Box 34, Folder 10)
  Incudes photographs and negatives (2 color, rest black and white)
- Slides and photo proof sheets - Vineyard 21, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Slides and photo proof sheets - Fredonia, May 11,1977 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Photographs - Washington grapes, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Photographs - Sites and soils, 1941-1942 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- POM cards and photo proof sheets - Weed control, November 1979, 1956-1975 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- POM cards - Meteorology, soils, and topography, ca. 1962-1976 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Photographs - Canopies, 1950-1965 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Photographs - Section 10, weed killing, and tillage, 1951-1953 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Photographs and negatives - Vineyard tools, 1947-1952 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Photographs - Nelson J. Shaulis, ca. 1978-1982 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  Includes press release regarding Peter Hemstad receiving the second annual Nelson J. Shaulis Advancement of Viticulture award.
- Photographs, photo proofs and negatives - Chemical control of weeds, 1957-1959 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  Includes letter from Dupont
- Photograph and slide notes, 1966-1970 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  Includes Ethrel, Alar, East, Central and West Tier, Delaware East Tier Herb.,
- Slides - Vineyard 21, July 27, 1977 (Box 34)
- Slides - Bud development, extra book slides, May 1974 (Box 34)
  Note - "Best slides held by C.P. for viticulture book and for C.P.'s research"
- Slides - Likely, vines, June 1977 (Box 34)
- Slides, October 1977 (Box 34)
- Slides - Cawtawba "scald" slides, 1974 (Box 34)
- Slides - Extra book slides, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides, 1953-1977 (Box 34)
- Slides - Not viticulture book, Geneva, Delaware, and White Riesling, October 24, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Vineyard 21, June 2, 1977 (Box 34)
- Slides - Vineyard 21, second roll, June 1977 (Box 34)
- Slides - Grape bud and shoot, 1974 (Box 34)
  "Best saved for book and CSP."
- Slides - Roll 2, to do after check in Fredonia, May 11, 1977 (Box 34)
- Slides - Apple root, English, 1933-1937 (Box 34)
- Slides - Vineyard 21, not pruned, April 20, 1977 (Box 34)
- Slides - Vineyard 21, set 2, am with all shoots/ pm removal of surplus shoots, and Loomis and Vineyard 21 winter and spring cold, May 20, 1977 (Box 34)
- Slides - Muscadines, Aurore, extra slides after book and projects, 1973 (Box 34)
  "CP has some muscadines"
- Slides - Grape base and count buds at doeskin, best saved for book, May 1974 (Box 34)
  "CSP has some for paper, C.S.P."
- Slides - Vineyard 21, cold injury, May 10, 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - Extra book slides, 1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - October seminar, to go to Australia, 1965-1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - 6, Geneva, Australia?, 1960-1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Oxidant stipple, Michigan, September 1, 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Oxidant stipple, Ives, October 12, 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Oxidant stipple, 25-var. experiment, October 12, 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Foliage 25-var. plot, Geneva duplicates, October 12, 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Oxidant stipple, Noah, October 22, 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Oxidant stipple var. effects, 1971-1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Senescence, 1966-1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Oxidant stipple as part of complex, 1966-1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Brown leaf, Charlotte Pratt, 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Mechanized harvesting, 1959-1964 (Box 34)
- Slides - Cornell harvest, 1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Childs mechanized harvesting, 1964 (Box 34)
- Slides - Harvester 2, 1964 (Box 34)
- Slides - Harvester, 1964-1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Mechanized harvester, Taylor and Standish, 1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Mechanized harvester (OW) at Taylors, 1966-1968 (Box 34)
- Slides - R. Schadine, NYSAES, Geneva, 1989 (Box 34)
  Note: "Color Charts not useful"
- Slides - Mechanized harvester loss slides, 1959-1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Shoot and vine growth, pruning, 1964-1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Mechanized harvesters, 1966-1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Brown leaf, 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides and notes - Umbrella, 1970-1975 (Box 34)
- Slides - GDC (Box 34)
  "G. Hucker slides on Geneva 1"
- Slides - Root and vine spacing, 1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Injury and drainage, ca. 1962-1973 (Box 34)
- Slides - Concord, oxidant stipple, close up, 1966-1971 (Box 34)
  "G. Hucker slides on Geneva 2"
- Slides - Concord, oxidant stipple, whole vine view, 1964-1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Concord, oxidant stipple, vineyard view, 1966-1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Concord, Brown leaf and drought, 1969 (Box 34)
- Slides - Concord, oxidant stipple, 1967 (Box 34)
- Slides - Leaf soundness, 2,4D, and senescence, 1966-1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - S. Dudley, weeds, October 1976 (Box 34)
  "Weeds, R. Joy, October 6, 1976, Keep - Don and project"
- Slides - S. Christy, glyphosate, October 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - V. lab, canopies, October 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - W. Riesling, glyphosate, October 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - Row 282, glyphosate, October 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - New York and United States yield and geography, 1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - British Columbia grapes, ca. 1950 (Box 34)
- Slides - European, 1961 (Box 34)
- Slides - German grapes, 1951-1961 (Box 34)
- Slides - West Washington raspberries, 1950 (Box 34)
- Slides - California grapes, 1950-1957 (Box 34)
- Slides - Iowa grapes and hops (Box 34)
- Slides - Hops, 1950 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup., vineyard 1, Childs, 1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. 4.5 feet x 9 feet, 1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. Y-top and T-top, 1962-1964 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. double trunks, 1962 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. vine vigor, 1962-1963 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. leaf temperature, 1963 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. heater position, 1963 (Box 34)
- Slides - Dup. 2,4-D redistribution, 1964 (Box 34)
- Slides - Shoot positioning, 1964 (Box 34)
- Slides - Childs oxidant stipple, October 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - Zinc deficiency, 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides and notes - Hail, 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - Aurore fruit set, 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - Couluse Catawba, 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - Vin. Lab canopies, October 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - North East Pennsylvania couluse problem, 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - North East Pennsylvania ridge established vines, 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - North East Pennsylvania mother garden and nursery, 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - Sites, Finger Lakes, 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - Muscadines, 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - Aurore plots, 1975 (Box 34)
- Slides - Crop sorting, Fredonia, 1976 (Box 34)
- Slides - Mechanized pruning, East Tier, 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Mechanized pruning 5x10, 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - West Tier, 1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - West Tier data (Box 34)
- Slides - Rootstocks, 1962-1970 (Box 34)
- Slides - Fruit set, Geneva, 1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Vine canopy, 1953-1972 (Box 34)
- Slides - Ives, rootstocks, 1966 (Box 34)
- Slides - Wind injury, ca. 1962-1966 (Box 34)
  "Not so valuable December 20, 1972"
- Slides - Harvesters, 1965-1971 (Box 34)
- Slides - Base buds, 1974 (Box 34)
- Slides - Vines, October 1977 (Box 34)